Finding aid for the Paulist Productions records LSC.2300
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1. Insight, 1960-1984
  - The Locusts Have No King [#157], 1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Script by Gilbert Ralston; script notes; photographs.
  - The Long Road Home [#426], 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun [one heavily annotated]; publicity material; photographs [includes off-camera shots of Martin Sheen].
  - Look Back to the Garden [#197], 1968 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Two scripts by John Meredyth Lucas [one annotated]; photographs.
  - The Love Song of the Cuckoo Birds [#347], undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - The Lovers [#147], 1964 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Script by John T. Kelley; photographs.
  - Madam [#184], 1967 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - The Man from Inner Space [#387], 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by William Peter Blatty [one heavily annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Man in the Cast Iron Suit [#398], 1976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Two scripts by John McGreevey; photographs.
  - Man in the Middle [#185], 1967 (Box 20, Folder unknown container)
  - The Man of the Year [#392], 1976 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by John V. Hanrahan [one annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Man Who Mugged God [#419], 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Two scripts by Richard Fielder [one heavily annotated]; publicity material; photographs [includes off-camera shots of Harold Gould and Warren Oates].
  - The Man Who Went Blue Sky [#373], 1974 and 1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun; photographs.
  - The Martyr [#139], 1963 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Two scripts [no writer credited]; photographs.
  - Matchpoint [#445], 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Script by Korby Siamis; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Missing Persons Bureau [#436], 1981 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Bliss [#424], 1981-1984 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by Christopher Keane [one annotated]; publicity material; staff and cast lists; photographs.
  - Mr. Johnson's Had the Course [#199], 1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Script by Stanford Whitmore [lightly annotated]; photographs.
  - The Mohawk [#375], 1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Script by Howard Fast; cast and staff lists; photographs.
  - Mummy [#196], 1968 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Carol Sobieski [one annotated]; photographs.
  - Murder in the Family [#158], 1965 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Script by Harry Fink [heavily annotated]; photographs.
  - The Needle's Eye [#435], 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Two scripts by Carol Evan McKeand; publicity material; list of ratings for Insight broadcasts in 1981-1982.
  - The Needle's Eye [#435] - photographs, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The Nitty-Gritty Once and Future Now [#188], 1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - No More Mananas [#337], 1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Two scripts by John Figueroa [annotated]; photographs.
  - No Tears for Kelsey [#307], 1969 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Three scripts by Jim McGinn [one heavily annotated]; study guides.
  - No Tears for Kelsey [#307] - photographs, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Nobody Loves a Rich Uncle [#346], 1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Two scripts by Edmund H. North; photographs.
  - Old King Cole [#324] - photographs, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Includes off-camera shots of Nichelle Nichols.
  - The Oleander Years [#171], undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Two scripts by Leon Tokatyan [one annotated]; photographs.
  - The One-Armed Man [#370], 1974 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Three scripts by Lan O'Kun [one annotated]; publicity material; cast and staff lists.
  - The One-Armed Man [#370] - photographs, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Includes off-camera shots of John Astin and Patty Duke.
  - Operation Dignity [#131], 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Two scripts [one incomplete; no writer credited]; photographs.
  - Out of the Depths [#389] - photographs, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - The Party [#339], 1971 and 1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by David Moessinger and Ed Waters [one annotated]; study guides; fan letter; photographs.
  - The Pendulum [#391], 1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Script by John McGreevey; photographs.
  - The Perennial Problem [#110/121], 1962 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    General
    Possibly broadcast as Christian Marriage.
    Three scripts [no writer credited]; photographs [includes scenes shot on the UCLA campus].
  - The Phony [#129], 1963 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - The Picture in Sobel's Window [#401], 1976 (Box 24, Folder unknown container)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun; cast and staff lists; photographs.
  - The Placement Service [#379], 1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by John T. Dugan [one annotated].
  - The Placement Service [#379] - photographs, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Plus Time Served [#418], 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by William McGivern [one heavily annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Poker Game [#210], 1969 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Script by Jack Hanrahan [lightly annotated]; study guides; photographs.
  - Politics Can Become a Habit [#179], undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Script by Bernard Abbene; photographs [includes off-camera shots of Diane Baker and Peter Fonda].
  - The Porous Curtain [#145], 1964 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Script by David Moessinger; photographs.
  - A Prayer from the Abyss [#333], 1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Script by Tom Caramagno; photographs.
  - Prince in the Apple Towns [#309], 1969 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by Thomas C. Caramagno [annotated]; photographs [includes off-camera shots of Jane Wyman].
  - The Prisoner [#140], 1964 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Outline by John Cogley; script by E. Sarsfield Waters; study guides; photographs.
  - The Prodigal Father [#378], 1975 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by Terry Sweeney, S.J.; photographs.
  - Prometheus Bound [#146], 1964 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by John Meredyth Lucas; photographs.
  - The Ragpicker [#130], 1962-1963 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Script [annotated; no writer credited]; photographs.
  - The Rebirth of Packy Rowe [#413], 1978 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun [one annotated]; publicity material.
  - The Rebirth of Packy Rowe [#413] - photographs, 1978 and 1997 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Includes off-camera shots of Jack Klugman and Bob Newhart.
  - The Rehearsal [#336], undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Script by Max Hodge.
  - Rehearsal [#393], 1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by Michael Alan Humm and Michael Jay Klassman; publicity material; study guide; photographs.
  - Rendezvous [#439], 1981 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Two scripts by David C. Field; publicity material; photographs.
  - Resurrection [#427], 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Three scripts by Ellwood Kieser, C.S.P.; publicity material; cast and staff lists; photographs.
  - The Resurrection of Joe Hammond [#362], 1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by Jack Hanrahan [one annotated]; photographs.
  - Reunion [#357], 1973 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Script by William P. McGivern; publicity material; cast and staff lists; photographs.
  - Ride a Turquoise Pony [#335], 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Three scripts by John Zodrow and David Zodrow [one annotated]; study guides.
  - Ride a Turquoise Pony [#335] - photographs, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Roommates on a Rainy Day [#356], 1973 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Script by Jim McGinn; study guides; cast and staff lists; photographs.
  - Sam [#316], 1969 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Three scripts by Carol Sobieski [two annotated]; study guides.
  - Sam [#316] - photographs, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - The Sandalmaker [#200], 1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Three scripts by David Moessinger; photographs.
  - Second Chorus [#417], 1978-1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Two scripts by Pete Cena [one heavily annotated]; cast and staff list; photographs.
  - Seed of Dissent [#183], 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Script by John Meredyth Lucas; photographs.
  - The Seven Minute Life of James Houseworthy [#319], 1970 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Script by John W. Zodrow; photographs.
  - Seventeen Forever [#386], 1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Two scripts by David Vowell [one annotated]; photographs.
  - The Sex Game [#403], 1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - She's Waiting for Us [#407], 1977 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Two scripts by Jim McGinn [one annotated]; cast and staff lists; publicity material; photographs.
  - Sinners Incorporated [#118], 1962 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - The Sixth Day [#434] (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun; publicity material; photographs.
  - A Slight Change in Plans [#420], 1979 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Script by Jim McGinn; photographs.
  - A Slight Drinking Problem [#405], 1977 and 1981 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Charlie Hauck; study guides; photographs.
  - A Small Statistic [#187], 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Script by Leon Tokatyan; photographs.
  - Snow in Summer [#178], undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Two scripts by Dehl Berti; photographs.
  - So Little Time [#448], 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Some Talk about Pool Rooms and Gin Mills [#181], 1967 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Somewhere Before [#381], 1981 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - The Sophomore [#127], 1962 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Script [no writer credited]; photographs [including scenes on the UCLA campus].
  - Stranger in My Shoes [#156], 1965 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Script by Gerry Day and B.W. Sandefur [annotated]; photographs.
  - The System [#348], undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Teddy [#442], 1981 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Thea [#429], 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by John McGreevey [one heavily annotated]; cast and staff list; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Theft [#371], 1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Two scripts by Michael Crichton [one annotated]; publicity material.
  - The Theft [#371] - photographs, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - A Thief Named Dismas [#166], undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by James Moser [heavily annotated]; photographs.
  - The 34th Hour [#201], 1968 (Box 30, Folder unknown container)
    Three scripts by James Moser.
  - The 34th Hour [#201] - photographs, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - This Side of Eden [#411], 1977 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - This Side of Eden [#411] - photographs, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
    Includes off-camera shots of Carol Burnett, Walter Matthau, and Ed Asner.
  - The Thousand-Mile Journey [#154], 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Script by John Meredyth Lucas [heavily annotated]; photographs.
  - A Thousand Red Flowers [#213], 1969 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Three scripts by John W. Bloch [one lightly annotated]; photographs.
  - Three-Cornered Flag [#198], 1968 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by John W. Bloch; photographs.
  - Thunder in Munich [#159] (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by Richard Breen [one heavily annotated]; photographs.
  - Trial by Fire [#177], undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Two scripts by John T. Dugan [one annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - Truck Stop [#359], 1981 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun [one annotated]; study guides; photographs.
  - The Truth about Time [#175], undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Script by E. Sarsfield Waters [annotated]; photographs.
  - Tuesday Night Is the Loneliest Night in the Week [#308], undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Three scripts by Maureen Daly [one heavily annotated].
  - The Tyrants [#135], 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Unfinished Business [#431], undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Two scripts by Jim McGinn; photographs.
  - Unidentified Bob Newhart episode - photographs, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - The Urchin [#142] - photographs, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Vision of Freedom [#116], 1962 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - The War of the Eggs [#336], 1971 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Michael Crichton; study guides.
  - The War of the Eggs [#336] - photographs, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Watts Made out of Thread [#204], 1968 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Two scripts by William P. Blatty; study guides; photographs
  - Welcome Home [#383], undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Two scripts by Lydia Wiggins [one heavily annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - When Heroes Fall... [#432], 1983 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Script by James Moser [heavily annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - When You See Arcturus [#372], 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Script by James E. Moser [annotated]; cast and staff lists; photographs.
  - Where Were You During the Battle of the Bulge, Kid? [#190], 1967 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Script by James E. Moser; study guides; photographs.
  - The White Star Garage [#444], 1982 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by Joseph Anderson; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Whole Damn Human Race...and One More [#191], 1967 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by David Karp; photographs.
  - Why Don't You Call Me Skipper Anymore? [#344] - photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Why Sparrows Fall [#170] - photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - ...With a Long Beard and Big Brown Eyes and Likes Peanuts [#163], 1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Script by John D.F. Black from as story by Gerry Day [annotated]; photographs.
  - A Woman of Principle [#327] - photographs, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - The Woodpile [#162] - photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - The World, The Campus, and Sister Lucy Anne [#160] - photographs, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - The Wrinkle Squad [#334], 1971 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Script by Thomas C. Caramagno; photographs.
  - Subseries 1. Scripts, 1962-1982
    This subseries consists of scripts that had been bound together in numerical order.
    - Productions #101-113, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Productions #114-119, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Productions #120-126, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Productions #127-133, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Productions #134-139, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Productions #140-145, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Productions #146-149, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Productions #150-153, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Productions #154-157, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Productions #158-162, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Productions #163-167, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Productions #168-170, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Productions #171-173, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Productions #174-176, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Productions #177-180, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Productions #181-183, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Productions #184-186, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Productions #187-189, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Productions #190-191, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Productions #192-193, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Productions #195-198, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Productions #202-204, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Productions #205-206, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Productions #307-308, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Productions #309-310, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Script #310 is missing at the time of processing.
    - Productions #312-313, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Productions #314-315, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Productions #316-318, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Productions #319-323, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Productions #324-329, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Productions #331-336, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Productions #337-341, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Productions #342-346, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Productions #347-353, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Productions #356-361, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Productions #362-366, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Productions #367-369, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Productions #370-371, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Productions #372-373, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Productions #374-375, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Productions #376-377, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Productions #378-379, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Productions #380-381, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Productions #382-385, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Productions #386-388, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Productions #389-391, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Productions #392-394, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Productions #395-397, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Productions #398-400, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Productions #401-402, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Productions #403-405, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Productions #407-409, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Productions #410-411, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Productions #412, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Productions #413-414, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Productions #415, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Productions #416-417, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Productions #418-420, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Productions #423, 425-426, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Productions #427-428, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Productions #429-431, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Productions #434-435, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Productions #436-437, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Productions #438-439, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Productions #440, 442, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Productions #443-445, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Productions #446-448, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Productions #449-450, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - "Father Kieser's intros", undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
      Contains text of Ellwood Kieser's narration for episodes #168-327.
  - Subseries 2. Scrapbook pages, 1960-1985
    This subseries contains pages from three-ring binder scrapbooks.
    - Clippings, publicity material, and set design, 1960-1961 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1962-1964 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1965-1966 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1967-1969 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Clippings and publicity material, 1970-1973 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1983-1985 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3. General files, 1960-199
    This subseries contains material regarding the Insight program in general, rather than any particular episode.
    - Administration, 1982-1985 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      Includes information on sales and rentals.
    - Benefit dinners, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Includes photographs of Edward Asner, Jack Albertson, Bob Hope, Martin Sheen.
    - Brochures, 1975-1978 (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
    - Cable television, 1997-1999 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Includes material regarding the sale of Insight to the Odyssey cable channel [now known as the Hallmark Channel].
    - Cast list, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
      Contains directory of actors appearing in Insight and Reflections episodes.
      Conditions Governing Access
      Portions of the contents of this folder are restricted and are unavailable for use. Inquiries regarding these materials should be directed in writing to UCLA Library Special Collections.
    - Catalog photographs, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Contains photos intended as illustrations in film catalogs.
    - Catalog photographs, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 1-5, Box 53, Folder 2-6)
    - Catalogs, 1971-1979 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Catalogs, 1979-1991 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Catalogs - non-Paulist Productions, 1969-1974 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      Contains catalogs from Association Instructional Materials and Walt Disney.
    - Clippings, 1976-1997 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Credit sheets, 1973-1983 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      Restrictions on Access
    - Director/writer list, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Contains directory of directors and writers working on Insight and Reflections programs.
    - Fact sheets, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Film inventories, 1960-1983 (Box 56, Folder 1-3)
      Contains records of former locations of film elements.
    - Film lists, ca. 1982 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      Contains lists of episodes categorized in a variety of different ways.
    - Financial, 1979-1980 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      Includes information about production and distribution expenses.
    - Motion picture film frames, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      Contains snippets of Super 8 film from a variety of productions.
    - Photographs - 100 series, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Photographs - 200 series, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Photographs - 300 series, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Photographs - 400 series, undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Photographs - 82/83 season, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Photographs - unsorted, 1961-1982 (Box 57, Folder 3-5)
    - Photographs - unsorted 1960s, 1961-1966 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Photographs - unsorted color prints, undated (Box 57, Folder 7-8)
    - Photographs - unsorted negatives, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Photographs - unsorted negatives, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Photographs - unsorted transparencies, 1978-1982 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Publicity material, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Publicity material - scrapbooks, 1962-1979 (Box 59-60)
    - Spanish-language material, 1972-1981 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      Includes catalogs in Spanish.
    - Story lines, 1967-1983 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      Includes lists of titles with synopses.
    - Story lines, undated (Box 58, Folder 6-7)
    - Study guides #360-366, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Study guides #367-377, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Study guides #378-388, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Study guides #396-402, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Study guides #404-411, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Study guides #413-418, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Study guides #419-431, 1979-1980 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Study guides #432-442, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Study guides #443-450, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Study guides #451-456, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Study guides - general, 1965-1979 (Box 62, Folder 1-3)
    - Videotape inventories, 1988-1992 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Videotape inventories, 1995-1998 (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
      Contains logs of tapes checked out to various television stations.
    - Vignette Films study guides, 1974-1979 (Box 63, Folder 1-4)
      Contains material on the re-edited and repackaged episodes that were distributed under the title "Vignette Films."
    - Library of Congress catalog cards, undated (Box 86, Box 87)
- Series 2. Capital Cities specials, 1977-1988
  This series contains material on television programs distributed by Capital Cities Communications.
  Productions are first listed in alphabetical order. Then a subseries consists of scripts in numerical order.
  - The Breadwinner [#824], 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Two scripts by Jim McGinn [one heavily annotated]; publicity material.
  - The Breadwinner [#824] - photographs, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Chicken [#809], 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Two scripts by Richard Fielder [one very heavily annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - Courage [#825], 1983 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun; publicity material; photographs
  - A Family of Winners [#808], 1979 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - A Family of Winners [#808] - photographs, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - A Friend In Deed [#807], 1978 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Script by Lan O'Kun; publicity material.
  - A Friend In Deed [#807] - photographs, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Girl on the Edge of Town [#811] - photographs, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Girl on the Edge of Town [#811] - publicity material, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Hang Tight, Willy Bill [#822], 1982 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Jim Moser [one annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - High Powder [#819], 1982 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Three scripts by Richard Fielder; publicity material.
  - High Powder [#819] - photographs, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - It Can't Happen to Me [#805], 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 3)